Hello Gas, in this video we will look at
technical analysis on ICC Lombard. We will also read and
scroll through. So I see a feature here called
Start. If you
like to trade index or futures in options,
then this feature can be very useful for you
because here
we get many options on a single screen. So when
I click here,
we see Nifty, Bank,
Nifty, profit and loss, buy call, buy food,
option change and order, and dynamic charts. All these make it
very easy for us to
wait. So now let's go to the chart. I have already placed the
ICC Lombard chart here.
Now let's look at the indicator
area. I will search for bowling here.
And look, the bowling option is visible.
We click on it and it will say,
according to
bowling, the price can go sideways from here.
Now if you think the price can
move upside down from here, then you can buy.
If you think the price can move sideways, then
you can sell the option.
Look at the channel, the channel page has opened for us,
here on the top side is the stock
details, here the expiry of three running months
is visible, you can enter any option according to your choice,
now if I enter an
ITP of 1040 on a
put option of 1040, the base details have opened
like opening point, closing point and last
point, now we will do this, this
video is for educational purpose only,
here I am entering the value quantity and quantity as per
my investment,
this is my order
limit, now I will click on the buy button, now
I will confirm my order and
see, my order has been confirmed,
so it is so easy to
trade instant futures by using Angel One Up, and
if you do not have an Angel One Minute account yet, then the
link is given in the description box,
you can open your demat account by going to it, so that's all
for today, see
in the next video, thanks for watching